[
    {
        "front": "What is the second planet in the solar system",
        "back": "Venus"
    },
    {
        "front": "What is the process called in which the plants harness energy from sunlight",
        "back": "Photosynthesis"
    },
    {
        "front": "Which cell is called the power house cell in our body",
        "back": "Mitochondria"
    },
    {
        "front": "Which scientist discovered gravity",
        "back": "Issac Newton"
    },
    {
        "front": "Which scientist discovered telephone",
        "back": "Alexander Graham Bell"
    },
    {
        "front": "Which planet in our solar system has an axis that is titled by 98 degrees",
        "back": "Uranus"
    },
    {
        "front": "Which American inventor is generally given credit for the invention of the lightning rod",
        "back": "Benjamin Franklin"
    },
    {
        "front": "The spider has how many legs",
        "back": "Eight"
    },
    {
        "front": "The reaction where two atoms of hydrogen combine to form an atom of helium is called what",
        "back": "Fusion"
    },
    {
        "front": "What is the name for trees that never lose their leaves",
        "back": "Evergreen"
    }
]